第 1 至 9 章复习与扩展：怎么做、做什么。所以你和英语的关系很艰难，我们来谈谈。
Chapters one through nine review and expansion how and what to do So you're in
你和英语的关系很艰难。我们来谈谈。也许你以前尝试过学
a tough relationship with English. Let's talk about that Maybe you've tried to pick
美式口音，却让你感到不舒服。也许你的家人认为
up an American accent before and it made you uncomfortable Maybe your family thinks
你不该改变。也许你试过但失败了，现在很沮丧。
that you shouldn't change. Maybe you've tried and failed now. You're frustrated
无论原因是什么，你和英语的关系并不令人满意。
Whatever the reason you've got an unsatisfying relationship with English.
我们就是来解决这个问题的。先把心态摆正。学习一整套
We're here to fix that Let's get your head in the right place. Learning a whole
语言确实是件大事，但你已经完成了最重的部分：
language is indeed a big deal, but you've already done all the heavy lifting, having
学完了语法和词汇。现在我们只是在微调，
learned the grammar and vocabulary. Right now, we're just doing the fine-tuning and
这就是你在最初一到六周练口音后应该期待的变化。
working on your accent. Here's what you should expect after the first one to six
周，具体取决于你的勤奋程度。
weeks, depending on your diligence.
Hello, my name is Rie Matsubara. I am taking American accent training. Hello, my
name is Rie Matsubara. I am taking American accent training. Hello, my name
is Manuel Rojas. I am taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Manuel.
I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Callie Lu.
Hello, my name is Kelly Luh, I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name
is Raymond Chun, I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Raymond
Chun, I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Narachem, I'm taking
American accent training. Hello, my name is Naz, I'm taking American accent
training.